Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
Before we move into the next section, let's review some of the important concepts that we have learned
在我们进入下一节之前，让我们回顾一下我们在本节学到的一些重要概念
in this specific section.
在本节中所学到的一些重要概念。
The first thing that we have learnt is, in Functional programming we focus on specifying what to do.
我们学到的第一件事是，在函数式编程中，我们专注于指定要做什么。
First of all, we converted the List to a stream.
首先，我们将List转换为一个流。
So, this is a sequence of elements
所以，这是一个元素的序列
and for each element what should be done. Allow it,
以及对每个元素应该做什么。允许它、
if it's only an odd number. Print the element out to the console. Do a cube of the number.
如果它只是一个奇数。将该元素打印到控制台。做一个数字的立方体。
So, for each element in this stream, we specified what needs to be done with it.
所以，对于这个流中的每个元素，我们指定了需要对它做什么。
We used numbers.stream() to convert a list into a stream and then we looked at a couple of important
我们用numbers.stream()将一个列表转换成一个流，然后我们看了几个重要的
methods on the stream.
方法。
We looked at filter which allows us to specify a condition. Only if
我们看了过滤器，它允许我们指定一个条件。只有当
that condition is matched, then the element would go further.
该条件被匹配，那么该元素将被进一步处理。
Otherwise, this element would be filtered out.
否则，这个元素就会被过滤掉。
So, if I have a list of numbers and I would want to allow only even numbers to go through or odd numbers
所以，如果我有一个数字列表，我想只允许偶数通过或奇数
to go through, then I can define a filter specifying what is the condition that needs to be checked on
通过，那么我可以定义一个过滤器，指定需要对数字进行检查的条件是什么。
the number. forEach is used to consume an element.
forEach是用来消耗一个元素的。
You take an element and print it.
你取一个元素并打印它。
That's what this specific thing helps us to do.
这就是这个具体的东西帮助我们做的事情。
We use map to map one value to another value.
我们使用map来将一个值映射到另一个值。
So over here, we took the number and we did a cube of it, number * number * number.
所以在这里，我们把数字拿出来，做了一个立方体，数字*数字*数字。
The other things which we looked at were Lambda Expressions.
我们看的其他东西是Lambda表达式。
You can see that filter, over here, uses a lambda expression. The map over here, uses another lambda expression.
你可以看到过滤器，在这里，使用一个Lambda表达式。这边的地图，使用了另一个Lambda表达式。
Over here, we are using a lambda expression to take a course and append the course.length() to it.
在这里，我们正在使用一个lambda表达式来获取一个课程，并将课程.length()附加到它上面。
We learnt that lambda expression is nothing but a simplified representation of a method.
我们学过，λ表达式只不过是一个方法的简化表示。
So, this lambda expression over here which takes a number and returns if it's even, is similar to the method
所以，这里的这个lambda表达式接收一个数字并返回是否为偶数，类似于方法
which we wrote in here. It takes a parameter called number and it returns if that specific number is
我们在这里写的。它接受一个名为number的参数，并返回该特定数字是否为
even. So, instead of writing this much amount of code, we would write a simple lambda expression.
偶数。所以，与其写这么多的代码，我们不如写一个简单的lambda表达式。
We also looked at Method References. Until now, we have used method references to call static methods.
我们还看了方法引用。到目前为止，我们已经使用方法引用来调用静态方法。
println is a static method on System.out.
println是System.out的一个静态方法。
So, we are saying, on the element call System.out.println element. And we use the method reference
所以，我们在说，在元素上调用System.out.println元素。而我们使用方法引用
to specify that. We also created method references using custom static methods.
来指定。我们还使用自定义静态方法创建了方法引用。
We created a method called isEven and we use the class name
我们创建了一个叫做isEven的方法，我们使用类名
: : isEven to call it. If you have not started doing the hands-on yet, I would recommend you to get
: isEven来调用它。如果你还没有开始动手实践，我建议你动手
your hands dirty and write as many functional programs as possible.
如果你还没有开始动手操作，我建议你动手写尽可能多的功能程序。
I'll see you in the next section.
我们在下一节再见。
Until then, bye bye.
在那之前，拜拜了。